但，我們可以直接跟他們買蛋糕，不是嗎？
是「可以」。
但那我們就少了「一起烤蛋糕」
外加我花在給他們拍馬屁，就為了那死配方，
一直苦苦求他們花的功夫，全都會付諸流水
而且我們說好了要「做」蛋糕，不是「買」蛋糕
而廣大神通的 Trixie 最討厭食言！
有什麼正在空氣中點燃
Something's burning in the air tonight
你鼻樑抬高，繼續放風箏
you turn your nose up, just keep flying that kite
沒事沒事沒事我沒事
I'm fine I'm fine I'm fine I'm fine
就算我跟你實說，你也會發飆
and if I told you, you'd be mad this time
我都在約談我同類
I've counseled all the ones like me
就在友誼學校，聽過沒
in the school of friendship, honestly
去過
做過
閉嘴
我能不能休息會
Can I get a break
我早就在這著地獄生存
I've been living in this hell already
我就是又個標把，步槍拿穩
I'm just another target, hold and steady
我一直以來都自己一人
I've been living on my own since then
我就是遊民，直到他們接管
I'm nomadic as they come take ten
我是如此廣大神通
I'm so great and powerful
我想你們都有聽過
I've bet you heard it all before
但我需要一直說
I need to repeat myself
一直沒進你耳朵
you weren't listening till now
你這次會發飆
You'll be mad this time
會發飆
Mad this time
你想我想我知你知
You think I think I know you know
你說你想你是最棒
you said you think you're the best
我更明白
I know better
你會發飆發飆發飆發飆
You'll be mad mad mad mad mad mad mad
當我知道我朋友有誰
when I know who my friends are
在你奪走一切之前
Didn't know what I wanted
我都不知道想要啥
till you took it all away
而現在我只想要
Now the only thing I want
度過每一天
is to live another day
(我希望你能)
(聽聽自己聲音)
大家都說會給你第二次機會
Everypony says they'll give you a second chance
但心底，他們從未忘記
but deep down they never forget
畢竟傷口這麼深
When the scars cut deep like that
我曾經破裂，不會在破一次
I was broken once, not gonna break again
只要我保持好，但老實說，遲早
if I do my best, or rather, "when"
我給你行禮但我懶得管你
I tip my hat to you but I couldn't care less
反正你這樣亂也懶得回禮
cuz you won't do the same despite your mess
你明白
You know it
我能長生不老，就像你
I can live forever just like you
工作，玩瘋，如此重複
working, playing hard, through and through
拼圖中間沒有並缺你
The pieces of the puzzle fit without you
只有我做得到我的程度
I'm the only pony who can do what I do
我站過你站的角度
I stood where you now stand before
但你聽不懂那些寓言
but you've got no clue of the metaphor
吵什麼
我們在一起很團結
沒算你，你就繼續發飆
without you, so stay mad
你這次會發飆
You'll be mad this time
會發飆
Mad this time
你想我想我知你知
You think I think I know you know
你說你想你是最棒
you said you think you're the best
我更明白
I know better
你會發飆發飆發飆發飆
You'll be mad mad mad mad mad mad mad
當我知道我朋友有誰
when I know who my friends are
在你奪走一切之前
Didn't know what I wanted
我都不知道想要啥
till you took it all away
而現在我只想要
Now the only thing I want
度過每一天
is to live another day